<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android Training</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome to App Training!</string>
    <string name="firstMessage">There are many things you should learn about Android App development.
    There will be no way to learn them from this short training class. There is a copy of the basic code you will need
        for this training class at a git repository. If you know how to use git you can clone that and open the project
        in android studio, or if you are a genius you can do it all from the command line.

       \n\n Oh yeah. Here is the link to the github code for this project. If you want to know how to add a hyper link
        in your string then all you have to do is add this android:autoLink="web" in the textview element that references your
        string. :)
        \n
        https://github.com/thinkvaughntest/AppTraining.git

             \n\n
        TO DO LIST:\n
        *Each student should create a github account and email their team leader their username.
        \n*Each Team leader should email me the list of usernames including their own.
        \n*Each student should clone this project from github to their local machine.
        \n*Each team member should create a branch with their name.
       \n*Each team leader should create a branch for the team. Team member branches should be
        merged with the Team Branch. Team Branch should be merged with the Training branch.

    </string>




    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_first_launched">First Activity</string>

    <string name="hello_world">This says it is the first activity, but really it is the second activity. The page that
    you just came from was actually the first activity. We are call this the first activity as it is the first
    activity launch from your application other than the Main Activity where you just came from. \n\n
    There are a few things you need to know about an activity like the activity life cycle and how to start an Activity.
    You can learn about that below or skip to the next activity.

    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_activity_life_cycle">Activity Life Cycle</string>
    <string name="title_activity_teams_page">Teams Page</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trainer">Trainer: Jon Vaughn</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trainer_webview">Trainer Webview</string>
    <string name="whyWebview">We will be mostly creating WebView applications. This allows you to
    turn any website into a quick native mobile application. Go on. Give it a try.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">splashScreen</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="todolist">
        *Each team should create a button with their team name in the layout file for this activity
    \n*Each team should create a function to launch their team activity when their team button is pressed.</string>
</resources>
